123glitter.com 2016-10-20

# 123glitter.com User Agreement - Privacy Policy and Terms of Use

123glitter.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site 123glitter.com. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTED**

123glitter.com is the sole owner of information collected on this website. We will not sell, share, or rent any information.

**CLIENT SIDE COOKIES**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the userï¿½s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. 

**SERVER LOG FILES**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track userï¿½s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**SHARING OF INFORMATION**

We may share demographic information with partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

**OUTGOING LINKS**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, 123glitter.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**MODIFICATION OF POLICY**

We reserve the right to modify this terms of service policy without notice. It is up to you to check for modifications periodically.

**TERMS OF USE**

All content and services provided by 123glitter.COM are for personal use only. You may not distribute any content or services on this site 123glitter without our written permission. Layouts, Glitter Graphics, Icons, Buttons, Banners and Other graphics design may not be modified and links to to 123glitter may not be removed. You may not use our content for unlawful purposes or anything prohibited by these terms and conditions.

123glitter is part of the NETAXIS IT SOLUTIONS (P) LTD , developed and designed by NETAXIS IT SOLUTIONS (P) LTD .. 123glitter.com, or any of it's employee's, management, or affiliates may not be held responsible or liable for any possible damages resulting in the use or misuse of 123glitter. The 123glitter logo, Layouts and Graphics is © 123glitter.com.

123glitter © 2005 and NETAXIS IT SOLUTIONS (P) LTD. All rights are reserved. All content, unless otherwise stated, is owned by MySpace-C123glitter.com.

If you feel that this site 123glitter.com is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us: netaxis@gmail.com

**THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org. 

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml

|   
---|---
